combofix.org 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy - COMBOFIX

If you need more Privacy Policy information or have any problems about our privacy policy, Please contact us at the? homepage’s? Contact Us Link ,at http://www.combofix.org, the visitors privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information that is collected and received? by http://www.combofix.org and how the information is used.

Website Log Files  
http://www.combofix.org makes use of log files. The information includes IP addresses, type of browser(Such as Microsoft IE,firefox,or google chrome,etc.) , date/time stamp, ISP, referring or exit URLs, track visitors’s movement around the website,the number of clicks, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google(google.com), as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.combofix.org.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.combofix.org .  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/

third-party ad networks use technology to the ads and links that appear at http://www.combofix.org send directly to your browsers.The third-party ad networks automatically receive your IPs when this occurs. JavaScrip ,cookies,etc. may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their ads and / or to personalize the ads by the content that you see.  
http://www.combofix.org has no any control on these cookies that are used by third-party ad networks. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these ad servers for more information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.combofix.org’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Need to disable cookies, you may do through you browser’s options,you can get more information about how to disable cookies from the browsers’ respective websites.
